ILGWU Memorabilia 5780 MB
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- ILGWU - buttons, Memorabilia (Box 13, Folder 15)
  "The Union for me, I.L.G.W.U."; "Support Your Local Garment"; two - "Look for the ILGWU Union Label"; some dupls. -- All items in box 13 were part of a donation of items by Lois Hartel, items were split and put into appropriate collections.
- ILGWU - Miscellaneous buttons, Memorabilia (Box 13, Folder 16)
  Buttons in several languages. -- All items in box 13 were part of a donation of items by Lois Hartel, items were split and put into appropriate collections.
- ILGWU - Miscellaneous, Memorabilia (Box 13, Folder 17)
  Buttons, pins, badge, tie tack, cuff links. Pins are dupls. Badge - "Delegate" from the 39th Convention. Gold tie tack and matching cuff links with the ILGWU Union label on them. -- All items in box 13 were part of a donation of items by Lois Hartel, items were split and put into appropriate collections.
- ILGWU - Badges, buttons, UNITE badge, Memorabilia (Box 13, Folder 18)
  Buttons - "Tell Congress NO NAFTA"; other items all duplicate things already in the collection -- All items in box 13 were part of a donation of items by Lois Hartel, items were split and put into appropriate collections.
- ILGWU - Badges, tie tack, cuff links, buttons, Memorabilia (Box 13, Folder 19)
  Buttons - duplicates -- All items in box 13 were part of a donation of items by Lois Hartel, items were split and put into appropriate collections.
- ILGWU - Patches, buttons, pins, etc., Memorabilia (Box 13, Folder 20)
  Most duplicate others in the collection, we have one unique that is triangle shaped, with pictures of an iron, scissors, sewing machine - "ILGWU, UIOVD", [Canadian Maple Leaf] -- All items in box 13 were part of a donation of items by Lois Hartel, items were split and put into appropriate collections.
- ILGWU - Miscellaneous souvenirs, Memorabilia (Box 13, Folder 21)
  Most have ILGWU label on them, others duplicate items in the collection. -- All items in box 13 were part of a donation of items by Lois Hartel, items were split and put into appropriate collections.
- ILGWU - sign, Memorabilia (Box 13, Folder 22)
  Sign made of paper over foam, light brown with dark brown lettering - "Int'l. Ladies' Garment Workers Union, A.F. of L.", "1000190" -- All items in box 13 were part of a donation of items by Lois Hartel, items were split and put into appropriate collections.
- ILGWU - Pins, buttons, Memorabilia (Box 13, Folder 23)
  Pin shaped like the letters of ILGWU, gold with white stones, buttons - "Health Care For All", "Plastic, Metal, Trucking, Warehouse & Allied Worker's Union." -- All items in box 13 were part of a donation of items by Lois Hartel, items were split and put into appropriate collections.
- CLUW [Coalition of Labor Union Women] - Patches, book mark, Memorabilia (Box 13, Folder 24)
  Patch - "CLUW"; book mark - "We didn't come here to swap recipes NOT THEN, 1974-NOT NOW, 1999!" -- All items in box 13 were part of a donation of items by Lois Hartel, items were split and put into appropriate collections.
- Bronzed shoe, Memorabilia (Box 13, Folder 25)
  One shoe bronzed as a 'souvenir' - "Lost by a scab who was later arrested, during the Dunkirk Lingerie Strike, 1969 in Dunkirk, NY." -- All items in box 13 were part of a donation of items by Lois Hartel, items were split and put into appropriate collections.
- ILGWU clothing labels, Memorabilia (Box 14, Folder 1)
  Various styles, sizes and shapes of 'Union Labels' used in clothing. All the labels have the ILGWU union bug on them
- ILGWU aprons, Memorabilia (Box 14, Folder 2)
  2 cloth aprons each with different material having the ILGWU union label on it. One apron is flowered and the other is a patchwork design.
- ILGWU aprons, Memorabilia (Box 14, Folder 3)
  3 cloth aprons all are white with blue Union Labels printed on them
- ILGWU scarves, Memorabilia (Box 14, Folder 4)
  3 satin scarves, all are red and white with blue Union Labels and "ILGWU" printed on them.
- ILGWU button-up cotton shirt, Memorabilia (Box 14, Folder 5)
  Button-up cotton shirt, flowered with the ILGWU Union Label printed on it.
- ILGWU 'convention' fans, 1992; Memorabilia (Box 14, Folder 6)
  Paddle fans (souvenirs) from the "41st ILGWU Convention, June 12, 1992, Fontainebleau Hotel, Miami Beach, Florida"
- ILGWU shower cap, Memorabilia (Box 14, Folder 7)
  White shower cap with blue ILGWU Union label printed on it.
- ILGWU flowered cotton material pieces, Memorabilia (Box 14, Folder 8)
  Pieces of cotton material, red, blue, yellow roses, with the ILGWU Union label printed in-between the flowers.
- ILGWU plastic 'bag', Memorabilia (Box 14, Folder 9)
  White plastic drawstring bag with blue 'ILGWU Union Labels' printed on it.
- ILGWU plastic aprons, Memorabilia (Box 14, Folder 10)
  Two aprons are flowered plastic with blue 'ILGWU Union Labels' printed on them. One apron is white with the blue union label printed on it.
- ILGWU cotton window curtain, Memorabilia (Box 14, Folder 11)
  One window curtain, patchwork designed material with "ILGWU Union Label" printed in some of the squares of the design.
- ILGWU cotton window curtain, Memorabilia (Box 14, Folder 12)
  Two window curtains with tie backs, patchwork designed material with "ILGWU Union Label" printed in some of the squares of the design.
- ILGWU ball point pen and key chain, Memorabilia (Box 14, Folder 13)
  Ball point pen and key chain, black with gold lettering "International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union"
- Unit House silver spoon, Memorabilia (Box 14, Folder 14)
  Silver spoon (souvenir) with a picture of a deer on the top of the handle with "Unity House, PA." in raised lettering.
- AFL-CIO News, vol. XXVI, No. 39, Sept. 26, 1981, Memorabilia (Box 14, Folder 15)
  "Solidarity Day!" issue of AFL-CIO News -- folders 15-18 were donated by Lois Hartel, Manager, Local 295, ILGWU
- Justice, Vol. LXIII, No. 9, September 1981, No. 10 October 1981, Memorabilia (Box 14, Folder 16)
  "Solidarity Day!" issues of Justice -- folders 15-18 were donated by Lois Hartel, Manager, Local 295, ILGWU
- Newspaper articles about Solidarity Day, 1981-1982; Memorabilia (Box 14, Folder 17)
  Pamphlets - Talking Union, No. 3, January 1982; Federationist, August & October 1981; Memo from Cope, September & October 1981; Pennsylvania Public Interest Coalition, October 1981; and articles from The Washington Post and The New York Times; 2 postcards -- folders 15-18 were donated by Lois Hartel, Manager, Local 295, ILGWU
- Solidarity Day banner, visor, 1981; Memorabilia (Box 14, Folder 18)
  Visor - "NAACP, Solidarity Day, March on Washington". Banner - "March for Jobs-Justice-Human Rights-Social Progress-AFL-CIO, Solidarity DayOn the National Mall, Washington, D.C." -- folders 15-18 were donated by Lois Hartel, Manager, Local 295, ILGWU
- ILGWU: buttons, campaign stickers, 1983; Memorabilia (Box 14, Folder 19)
  Buttons - White with yellow trim - "Local 23-25 - ILGWU, Shop Rep"; White with yellow trim - "Local 23-25 - ILGWU, Rep de Taller"; (2) - 1-White with black lettering & 1- White with blue lettering - "International Ladies'Roll-Back Imports, Washington, D.C., May 4, 1983" Stickers - booklet of stickers that look like $1 stamps - "I did my share, voluntarily contributed, receipt issued by ILGWU...Roosevelt-Truman"
- ILGWU rubber stamp, Memorabilia (Box 14, Folder 20)
  Rubber stamp with ILGWU union label
- ILGWU - wooden block, Memorabilia (Box 14, Folder 21)
  Wooden block written on with a pen, signed by some union members. Carved on one side is "Int. Ladies Garment, Union Made, ILGWU, AFL-CIO Workers Union"
- ILGWU - ball point pens, markers, pencil, Memorabilia (Box 14, Folder 22)
  9 ball point pens, 1 pencil and 2 markers - "Save a Job: Look for the Union Label"; 4 ball point pens - "Look for the Union Label, You'll Know it's American-Made"; 1 marker for "80th Anniversary, Northeast, Western Pennsylvania and Ohio Dept."; 1 ball point pen for "Thirty-eighth Convention, Hollywood, Florida..."; 1 ball point pen each for - "Atlantic Apparel Contr. Assn.", "Northeastern, Western Pa. and Ohio Department", "International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union..." and "Coalition of Labor Union Women"
- ILGWU bookends, Memorabilia (Box 14, Folder 23)
  Plastic and metal bookends with lettering "Int. Ladies Garment Workers Union, Union Made, ILGWU, AFL-CIO, Made in U.S.A."
- Coalition of Labor Union Women, paper weight, Memorabilia (Box 14, Folder 24)
  White marble with metal seal of the "Coalition o f Labor Union Workers"
- ILGWU - decks of playing cards, Memorabilia (Box 14, Folder 25)
  2 decks of playing cards, in a plastic box with lettering "Int. Ladies Garment Workers Union, Union Made, ILGWU, AFL-CIO", "Symbol of Decency Fair Labor Standards and the American Way of Life"
- Unity House picture viewers, Memorabilia (Box 14, Folder 26)
  2 souvenir picture viewers one with lettering "Unity House, Famed Pocono Resort Hotel", one has a photo of some unidentified women
- ILGWU Mug and Unite House plastic cup, Memorabilia (Box 14, Folder 27)
  Plastic cup/glass with lettering "Unity House, Famed Pocono Resort Hotel" and plastic mug with lettering "If it's gonna be it's up to me a Union Woman" with the ILGWU union bug
- ILGWU wrist watch, Memorabilia (Box 14, Folder 28)
  Wrist watch with brown leatherette band, and the ILGWU union bug on the face of it.
- Miscellaneous name cards, ribbons, etc., 1995-1997; Memorabilia (Box 15, Folder 1)
  Name tags for Joseph Lombardo, [UNITE, Local 155, Retiree] -- 2 red ribbons - [Delegate]
- Roll of adhesive labels -, 1994; Memorabilia (Box 15, Folder 2)
  White labels with Red and Blue lettering - "UNITED in 1994" with a 'Union Label'
- Hand book for Label Custodians, 1924; Memorabilia (Box 15, Folder 3)
  "Hand book on the Sanitary Label" - binding is weak, but bound booklet for use by Label Custodians
- Miscellaneous - adhesive union labels, booklet of ILGWU stamps, glass cleaning cloth, Memorabilia (Box 15, Folder 4)
  Glass cleaning cloth - "Symbol of decency, fair labor standards and the American way of life."; Monthly per capita (1000 stamps) all "ILGWU"; bumper stickers "Please look for this union label when you shop!" [purple with white lettering]
- Stencils for posters, Memorabilia (Box 15, Folder 5)
  Purple stencils to use to print posters - "TONITE! George Meanyetc.
- "Union Shop" signs, a California Legislature Assembly, Certificate of Recognition, and a program from the Northern California Labor Hall of Fame, 1990; Memorabilia (Box 15, Folder 6)
  Signs - "Union Shop, Open from 8 a.m. to 6 p.m. Cleaners and Dye Workers"; "Union Shop, this is to certify that this Laundry Establishment is in accordance."; program - Northern California Labor Hall of FameJuly 27, 1990"; "Certificate of Recognition - Presented to Jenny Matyas...."
- Miscellaneous - aspirin box, mirror, calendars, 1974-1977; Memorabilia (Box 15, Folder 7)
  Pocket calendars advertising ILGWU, for both 1974 and 1977, pocket - flip open mirror, with advertising for the ILGWU on the inside of cover, box made to hold a few aspirin with advertising for the ILGWU on the cover.
- Miscellaneous - hat, pencil, rulers, key chains, sewing kit, Memorabilia (Box 15, Folder 8)
  All items advertise the ILGWU
- Paper tape measure, gold medallion, 1964; Memorabilia (Box 15, Folder 9)
  Medallion - "First Union Health Center, Fifteen Anniversary" back side - "On November 20, 1963, President John Kennedy signed the act of the U.S. Congress authorizing the medal to commemorate the .", Paper tape measure - white with red and blue lettering
- Sample ballot for Knitgoods Workers' Union, Local 155. Certificate from the National Council of Senior Citizens. Dues card from the ILGWU, Local 155. Memo, 1968-1972; Memorabilia (Box 15, Folder 10)
  Certificate - "New York State Council of Senior Citizensthe Retired Officers Club of the ILGWU is an Official Member group."; Sample ballot for information purposes; Empty dues card; Minutes from a meeting June 12-14, 1972
- Paper weight, 1983; Memorabilia (Box 15, Folder 11)
  Gold and black metal paper weight - "Knitgoods Workers Union, ILGWU, AFL-CIO, 50th Anniversary 1983"
- ILGWU - 'hats', Memorabilia (Box 15, Folder 12)
  All hats are red/white/blue - "ILGWU" with a union label printed on them.
- ILGWU - 'hats', 1973; Memorabilia (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Knitgoods Workers Union - key chain, 1973; Memorabilia (Box 15, Folder 14)
  Gold key chain with green background. "Knitgoods Workers Union, Local 155, 40th Anniversary, 1933-1973"
- ILGWU - 'hats', Memorabilia (Box 15, Folder 15)
- ILGWU Convention 'fan', 1992; Memorabilia (Box 15, Folder 16)
  Souvenir 'fan' from the "41st ILGWU Convention, June 12, 1992, Fontainebleau Hotel, Miami Beach, Florida"
- ILGWU - 'hats', Memorabilia (Box 15, Folder 17)
- ILGWU - 'hats', Memorabilia (Box 15, Folder 18)
- ILGWU - 'hats', Memorabilia (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Bus tickets for Local 155, ILGWU 25th Jubilee Outing, 1958; Memorabilia (Box 15, Folder 20)
  Bus tickets - "Local 155, ILGWU, 25th Jubilee Outing, June 27-29, 1958, for one person from New York to Unity House" and tickets for the return trip
- Miscellaneous, 1918-1975; Memorabilia (Box 15, Folder 21)
  "Anti-Nazism, Fascism, ILGWU $50,000 Fund 25[cents]"- stamp booklet; envelope with a cancelled "Collective Bargaining' stamp; "Certificate Day's Work", "Relief day for war sufferers, Washington's Birthday, February 22, 1918."; card with announcement in English, Hebrew and Italian - "To all White Goods Workers, all employees of your shop are requested to attend an Important Meeting....Local 62"
- Local signs for ILGWU convention tables, and wooden block holders, Memorabilia (Box 15, Folder 22)
  Local signs for ILGWU Convention tables and wooden block holders. It was a tradition for Union members to bang the blocks on the Convention tables to signify their approval or disapproval.
- ILGWU - membership and dues cards, union dues book, 1937-1938; Memorabilia (Box 15, Folder 23)
  Blank membership/dues cards for 1937, 1938 and one dues book
- Sewing kit, Memorabilia (Box 15, Folder 24)
  One small sewing kit in case, and correspondence that accompanied it.
- ILGWU - Pins, buttons, Memorabilia (Box 15, Folder 25)
  Two designs - Blue with a picture of the union label, and white with a cartoon of Uncle Sam in bed with the caption "Health Care for All!"
- ILGWU: badges, belt buckle, 1986; Memorabilia (Box 15, Folder 26)
  Badges - one for Guest, one for Press - both from Thirty-ninth Convention of ILGWU, Hollywood, Florida, May 1986; belt buckle is bronze in color, and has a picture of the union label (transferred from collection 5780/117)
- ILGWU - small banner, 1963; Memorabilia (Box 15, Folder 27)
  Banner - maroon with gold lettering, Chinese, and English "Chinese Labor Observation Team 1963" (transferred from 5780/118)
- Framed memorabilia - Newspaper clipping/picture of "Mrs. Roosevelt"; a thimble and letter from Del Monte Hickey Company, presented to Pietro Paolella., 1933; Memorabilia (Box 16, Folder 1)
  Frame with a newspaper clipping of "Mrs. Roosevelt accepting first NRA Coat label", letter from Del Monte Hickey Company with a sewing thimble attached. "Presented to Pietro Paolella--Retired Member of Local 48"
- Plaque - Presented to the ILGWU from the Workmen's Circle Home & Infirmary for the Aged, 1976; Memorabilia (Box 17, Folder 1)
  "Presented to the International Ladies' Garment Workers Union at the 25th Anniversary Celebration of the Workmen's Circle Home & Infirmary for the Aged" -- Nov. 7, 1976
- Broadsides, Charters, Proclamation, 1916-1947; Memorabilia (Box 18, Folder 1)
  Broadside mounted on wood - Hebrew and English - "The New Post", May 3, 1916; Charter mounted on wood - ILGWU Local 82, Sept. 18, 1947; Charter mounted on wood - ILGWU, Local 9, Feb. 21, 1927
- Proclamation, Charter, 1940; Memorabilia (Box 18, Folder 2)
  [in folder] - Proclamation - "Lyndon B. JohnsonKnow yeLouis Stulberg, of New York I have nominated, and, by and with the advice and consent of the Senate, do designate him an Alternate Representative of the United States of America to the Twenty-third session..."; Charter - ILGWU, Local 98, April 13, 1940
- Certificates, plaque, awards, charter, etc., 1917-1980; Memorabilia (Box 19, Folder 1)
  Charter mounted on wood - ILGWU, Local 82, May 15, 1917; "American Veterans Committee, presents this Special Award to the "ILGWU" on its 75th Anniversary"; "State of New York Dept. of Labor Certificate of Commendation to "ILGWU""; Presented in grateful appreciation to "ILGWU" on the historic occasion of the 60th Anniversary of Histadrut-the General Federation of Labor in Israel..."
- Certificates, plaque, awards, charter, sketch, etc., Memorabilia (Box 19, Folder 2)
  "In recognition and appreciation of his Constructive Inspiration Constant the United-Italian American Labor Council" to Louis Stulberg; "In the annals of American labor historyfor Chick Chaikin" from Social Democrats; Pencil sketch by P.C. Wilson; "Statement by the AFL-CIO Executive Council on Louis Stulberg..."; Award of Appreciation honoring Jasper Peyton, Jr....ILGWU"
- Certificates, plaque, awards, charter, sketch, etc., Memorabilia (Box 19, Folder 3)
  "The President of the United States of America awards this Presidential Medal of Freedom to David Dubinsky"; "Il Presidente della RepubblicaCavaliere di Gran Croce Louis Stulberg; State of Israel Bonds, Scroll of Special Merit awarded in appreciation to Louis Stulberg..."; American Veterans Committee, Dag Hammarskiold Memorial Award - 1979 to Sol C. Chaikin..."; In recognition of Distinguished Service this Scroll of Honor is presented to Sol C. Chaikin..."
- Certificates, plaque, awards, charter, sketch, etc., Memorabilia (Box 19, Folder 4)
  "Certificate of Appreciation, 40th Anniversary, New York City Planning Commission, 1938-1978Sol C. Chaikin"; Jewish Labor Committee, National Trade Union Council for human rights presents this scroll of appreciation to Sol C. Chaikin"; "Souvenir diploma awarded to Sol C. Chaikin for participating in the 10th International Games of 'Hapoel'...; "Manhattan 28, American Veterans Committee presents this Citizen First to Sol C. Chaikin..."; Plaque - "The 1980 Malcolm Dodds Award presented to Sol C. Chaikin for being the World's Greatest Union Leader Conductor"
- Award mounted on wood, 1983; Memorabilia (Box 20, Folder 1)
  "The David L. Clendenin Award, this plaque in honor awarded to David Dubinsky"
- Cartoon mounted on wood, Memorabilia (Box 20, Folder 2)
  Cartoon mounted on wood - "Presented to President David Dubinsky by the Executive Board and Officers of the Snow Suit Department of the Cloak Joint Board"
- Framed award, 1973; Memorabilia (Box 20, Folder 3)
  "La Comision Especial Etiqueta Professional"
- Award mounted on wood, 1986; Memorabilia (Box 20, Folder 4)
  "Consumer Award of Merit, Presented to Sol "Chick" Chaikin"
- Award mounted on wood, 1984; Memorabilia (Box 20, Folder 5)
  "The Massachusetts AFL/CIO proudly designates Sol Chick Chaikin recipientGompers-Murray-Meany Award"
- Award mounted on wood, 1978; Memorabilia (Box 20, Folder 6)
  "Humanitarian Award to Sol C. ChaikinHistadrut, The Israel Labor Federation"
- Inaugural speech of Pres. Kennedy, 1969; Memorabilia (Box 20, Folder 7)
  "The Inaugural Address of John Fitzgerald Kennedy" [mounted on wood] "Presented to Sol C. Chaikin"
- ILGWU Scrap book, Memorabilia (Box 21, Folder 1)
  The Scrap book has the ILGWU seal on the front and inside there are numerous, citations, awards, and some photos attached to the pages
- Local 23-25 News, Vol. 30, no. 5 (Oct. 1981), Memorabilia (Box 22, Folder 1)
- ILGWU souvenirs, Memorabilia (Box 22, Folder 2)
  1 Sewing kit, 1 rain hat, 1 round felt patch (red, white, blue), 1 ILGWU patch, 2 ILGWU rulers (1 cloth, 1 plastic)
- ILGWU posters, Memorabilia (Box 23, Folder 1)
  2 posters from Argentina, with Union Member signatures (rolled and in need of steam flattening), 1 paper board poster, with a picture of a man diving into water with the following lettering "To Our Good Friend David Dubinsky, Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America", with signatures of Union Members
- ILGWU advertisement, 1991; Memorabilia (Box 23, Folder 2)
  "Join the drill on March 27 -- Fire Safety is Fashionable" (gives instructions on fire safety)
- ILGWU Charter of Affiliation, 1982; Memorabilia (Box 23, Folder 3)
  "Charter of Affiliation with the National Council of Senior Citizens, Inc..This is to certify that the Retired Officers of the International Ladies Garment Workers Union is an Official Member Group of the National Council of Senior Citizens, Inc."
- ILGWU election advertisement, Memorabilia (Box 23, Folder 4)
  "II) To nominate Pat Moynihan - so we can get rid of Senator Buckley - you must vote in the Democratic primary on Tuesday, September 14th."
- ILGWU sign, Memorabilia (Box 24, Folder 1)
  Clear plastic sign with lettering. ILGWU seal, Archives
- ILGWU Plaque, 1985; Memorabilia (Box 25, Folder 1)
  Wooden plaque - "The New York Union Label and Service Trades Department." [honoring ILGWU for their help]
- David Dubinsky photo album (empty), Memorabilia (Box 25, Folder 2)
  Empty photo album with "David Dubinsky" monogrammed on the front
- Newspaper print plate, 1919; Memorabilia (Box 25, Folder 3)
  A newspaper printing plate for the "Justice" - vol. I, no.1, January 18, 1919
- Statue of Liberty print plate, Memorabilia (Box 25, Folder 4)
  A printers plate in the shape of the Statue of Liberty
- ILGWU Scrap book, 1981; Memorabilia (Box 25, Folder 5)
  Scrap book - "ILGWU - America's Next Great Designer Awards - 1981 Competition"
- Photo album/scrap book, 1950; Memorabilia (Box 26, Folder 1)
  Scrap book - has lettering on the cover - "Golden Jubilee Convention, Atlantic City - 1950" - contents is one certificate - "This is to certify Dolores S. Fisher served as a duly accredited Delegate to the Golden Jubilee Convention"
- Bucilla Initial Book, Memorabilia (Box 26, Folder 2)
  Catalogue from - Bucilla - Initial Book, assortment of 390 embroidery letters to be transferred with a hot iron
- Medical card; Union Clothing label; Ticket to House of Representatives Art Gallery; Reserved Platform Ticket; Access near Platform but not on Platform - ticket; ticket to meet Walter Mondale and Geraldine Ferraro, 1953; Memorabilia (Box 26, Folder 3)
  2 medical cards for Jennie Falcone, in an envelope that states - Good only from January 1, 1953 through December 31, 1953 - Medical Service Card (ILGWU Union Health Center); "House of Representatives, Admit Bearer to the Visitor's Gallery, James T. Molloy, Doorkeeper, 99th Congress"; "ILGWU Campaign Committee and Democratic National Committee Garment Center Rally."; "ILGWU Campaign Committee and Democratic National Committee Garment Center Rally."; "at a Buffet Luncheon immediately after the Rally - The Central Federal Savings Bank"
- ILGWU - souvenir bag, Memorabilia (Box 26, Folder 4)
  White souvenir bag with blue and red lettering. "Look for the union label.", "Think of it as a little American Flag in your clothes" - and an ILGWU union label in the center
- JUSTICE - souvenir program, 1944; Memorabilia (Box 26, Folder 5)
  Commemorating 25th Anniversary of Justice official organ and 25 years of service by its editor, max D. Danish.
- Stocks and bonds, 1917-1943; Memorabilia (Box 26, Folder 6)
  2 bonds from The Workingmen's Co-operative Publishing Association; 2 stock certificates from The New York Call Printing Co., Inc.; Stock subscription from International Union Bank; Stock certificate from Local 91 Realty Corporation
- Certificate from State of Arkansas, 1957; Memorabilia (Box 26, Folder 7)